Friends, if you want to make a big name in the health insurance business,
you
want to do motor insurance business, you
want to do non-motor insurance, all these
codes are available under one working.
Friends, if you want to
work on a part-time or full-time basis along with your job, business, or professionalism, then
you can easily join this working. The
amount of money in the insurance business is not available in any other business, friends.
ICC Lord General
Insurance Company is about which I will
tell you how to become an agent of ICC Lord,
how you can do health insurance,
how you can do motor insurance,
how you can do non-motor fire and bugger
insurance. These
three working codes are genuinely available under one working code.
Friends, you can join us on an all-over India basis
in this agency module.
My name is Yogendra Verma.
I am the Recruitment Manager at ICC Lord.
Generally, I help people by
providing them a good and reliable platform
and generally I also provide them training
so that they can earn big and
excellent money in a month.
After joining the platform, you can easily earn at least
₹2500000 per
month, both in your job and
business. You just need to trust this company and its
working. Before proceeding further,
you need to subscribe to my channel,
share, comment, and
click the bell icon to receive all the latest
updates, ensuring you
receive all the new and exciting information. So, let's
quickly see
how to become an ICC Lombard agent. What are the
benefits of joining this company, what benefits will it bring to you,
and what is the joining process, and what are the
mandatory conditions after joining.
What formalities will you have to complete
so that your code remains valid? I will
share all the information with you quickly. So,
friends, IC Lord is one of the
best general insurance companies. Health insurance is provided here in a
very excellent manner and is
well-matched.
Motor insurance is also available here. Many
people take the ICC Lord code for motor insurance as well,
and
you can also get non-motor insurance here through this code.
Earnings range from 15 to 35 or 40.
In motor insurance, payouts range from 2 to 25
and in non-motor insurance,
payouts range from 15 to 30.
You can easily do all three types of work with a single code.
There is a fully digital
platform for everything. General
learning training is provided through Microsoft Teams
and Zoom meetings. There is
no need to physically visit any branch.
We
teach and guide everything online and to join it, it will be
necessary to appear for a mandatory exam.
A person can take three types of codes:
one for life, one for health and one for general. Just
as it is mandatory to appear for the exam for life insurance, similarly it will be
mandatory to appear for the exam for general insurance as well. So, there is a fee for the IRDA exam here.
After paying the fee of ₹1, there is a list of
documents which I have written here.
These documents are
We will also share the learning material with you. So
friends, this is the general
process, payout and all the working that I
told you about the company, but
after joining, you have to follow some mandatory conditions.
You get this general insurance code only when you make a
commitment. In the first month, you have to activate
your code from a health insurance business, only
then you can do motor
insurance work. It will be
necessary to do four health policies in a year.
You have to pay a minimum premium of Rs 8000 per year
and
sell at least four health policies. This will be a mandatory condition, only then
your health code, motor code and non-
motor code will be activated. There is
no condition in motor, you can do as many policies as you want. There is no condition
in non-motor, you can do as many
policies as you want. But until you do
not log in to the health insurance business, the
motor code and non-motor code will
not open or start. So please keep in mind that to
do this code, you will be
required to do health insurance work and there
is ample scope for working in health insurance.
Yes, policies are sold easily,
people trust IC Lord, of which
you will get genuine benefits friends and
IC Lord is the number one genuine company in giving claims, be it
health claim,
motor claim or non-motor claim, this is
the very very superior company, so
friends, you must have understood this profile and working,
how to become an agent quickly, so I will share its list of
documents with you and
after sharing the documents, you have to pay a fee of Rs 1000,
after that my team will conduct a
zoom session with you, will conduct a video session in
which I will explain all this working to you and get
your code processed, hello your
friend Yogendra B